# **Andrew Park**

(714)-869-5607 • 70 Morningside Dr, New York, NY • ajp2259@columbia.edu

#### **CAREER PROFILE**

Student at Columbia University with data analysis experience interested in research within the fields of game theory, risk management, and economic policy. Skills include proficiencies in various programming languages, analysis of datasets, and visualization of statistics.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### COLUMBIA DAILY SPECTATOR

Graphics Reporter | New York, NY

Sep. 2020–Present

- Collaborate with journalists at the Columbia Daily Spectator to produce both data-driven and illustrative visuals to tell a story and complement the journalist's reporting
- Work closely on data reporting projects with other members of the Graphics team
- Analyze datasets that are acquired from both public and private databases with Python packages
- Utilize R and Adobe Illustrator to create original visualizations that present statistics in a coherent manner
- Attend weekly meetings to discuss the work agenda for the upcoming weeks, as well as circulate novel
  article ideas

#### **STEAMPORT**

Program Coordinator | Orange County, CA

Aug. 2019-May 2020

- Led free STEM learning experiences involving both hands-on experiments and educational presentations to elementary school students
- Organized monthly sessions with librarians and school directors in the Orange County area
- Designed new lesson plans for the 2019-2020 school year and revised lesson plans created by past member

## Student Volunteer | Orange County, CA

Dec. 2018-Aug. 2019

- Led and assisted other members at monthly sessions across libraries in the Orange County area
- Reviewed lesson plans to both revise errors and make improvements to improve the students' understanding of the material

## **EDUCATION**

**Columbia University** | Bachelor of Arts in Economics-Mathematics

Expected May 2024

• GPA: 3.85/4.0, Dean's List

## **SKILLS**

## Languages

• English (Fluent), Korean (Native)

## **Programming**

• Java, Python (pandas, Jupyter Notebook), Matlab, R, C, Javascript (d3), RegEx

## Other Software

• Adobe Illustrator, Microsoft Office Suite, Git

#### Coursework

- COMS W3134: Data Structures and Algorithms
- ECON UN1105: Principles of Economics
- ECON UN3211: Intermediate Microeconomics
- MATH UN1201: Calculus III
- MATH UN1202: Calculus IV
- PHIL UN3411: Symbolic Logic
- STAT UN4203: Probability Theory (In Progress, Summer 2021 A)